sheridan.com.au 2018-09-08

# Privacy

This website under the domain name sheridan.com.au (the "Website") is owned and operated by Sheridan, a division of Sheridan Australia Pty Ltd which is part of the HanesBrands Companies (collectively called "Sheridan", "we, "us" or "our" in this policy).

Your privacy is very important to us and we will always act to protect your personal information. We take this responsibility seriously and are very careful about how and when your personal information is collected, used and shared. This statement outlines what our commitment is, why we need to collect personal information, who we may share that personal information with and how you may request access to and correction of the personal information that we hold. This statement relates to personal information we collect through the Website.

back to top

The type of personal information we collect is dependent on the type of service or interaction you wish to receive. Personal information we collect may include: your name, address, phone and other contact details (fax, email etc), date of birth, gender, merchandise information (purchases, orders etc), method of payment. Sometimes we will also collect other personal information, such as where you shop or what your interests are, so that we can improve our service and product offering to you. You may decide not to provide your personal information to us. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide you with access to certain information, products, or services. We do not store your credit card details in any way; they are secured by 128-bit SSL encryption and transmitted directly by you to our payment processing provider.

back to top

The personal information we collect is generally supplied directly by you through our Website. For example, the details you provide us when you place an order, open an account, subscribe to our emails, join a mailing list, enter a competition, submit an enquiry, or provide feedback to us. There are also certain situations in which we may collect personal information about you from someone else. For example we may collect information from third parties including public sources, our related companies, your organisation, your representatives and information service providers.

We also receive and store certain types of information through the use of 'Cookies', when you interact with Sheridan via the Internet. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are placed on your computer's hard drive through your web browser. Most Internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to disable or to warn you when cookies are used. We recommend that you leave your cookies enabled as they allow our systems to recognise your browser and provide quicker and easier use of our Website.

back to top

We collect personal information for a number of reasons, including to: deliver, administer and improve the products and services that we offer you, complete other transactions with you or on your behalf, protect against fraud or theft, provide offers and promotions that we consider may be of interest or benefit to you, conduct market research, work with our related companies and service providers, maintain and update our records, protect and uphold the rights, property and safety of us, our customers and others, facilitate acquisitions and potential acquisitions of our business and assets and generally provide you with a premium customer experience.

back to top

We may exchange your personal information with other HanesBrands Companies and companies who perform part of our service delivery or provide other support services to us, for example, organisations that assist us with postal, data processing and analysis, research, mail, promotional, customer contact, technology, banking, payment, debt collection and maintenance services. We may otherwise use or disclose your personal information with your consent (or if we have given you notification of the intended use or disclosure and you have not objected to that use or disclosure) or where required or authorised by law, which may include emergency situations and assisting law enforcement agencies.

Third parties to whom we disclose personal information may be located in Australia, United States of America, United Kingdom, Hong Kong, Philippines and other countries.

back to top

This Website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties (such as YouTube). Be aware that this privacy statement only applies to the personal information that we collect through this Website. We are not responsible for the collection, storage or usage of personal information at any such third party websites and you should review the privacy policy of any Website you visit.

back to top

We welcome visitors from outside Australia. However, this is an Australian based website and this privacy statement governs the personal information collected at this Website irrespective of where you may be located when you visit the Website and interact with it. This means your personal information may be stored outside the country in which you are located and any government authorities which have jurisdiction over the Website may be entitled to access any personal information provided.

back to top

We will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised person under the age of 18. If you are under 18 years of age you must not submit any personal information to us unless you have the consent of, and are being supervised by, a parent or legal guardian.

back to top

As permitted by applicable law, you may have a right of access, rectification and delegation of information collected by you, and the right to oppose, for legitimate reasons, the processing of this information. To exercise these rights, please contact us using the contact details below. We request that you provide us with as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged to cover our costs of providing that information to you. In certain circumstances, we may not be required by law to provide you with access or to correct your personal information. If that is the case, we will give you our reasons for that decision. Where we decide not to update your personal information, you can request us to attach to the personal information a statement of the update sought.

We take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

If you have any questions or feedback about privacy, please contact our Privacy Officer at [privacyofficeraustralasia@hanes.com](mailto:privacyofficeraustralasia@hanes.com) or call (+61 3) 8862 1400. For information about privacy generally, or if your concerns are not resolved to your satisfaction, you may contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/) and on 1300 363 992.

back to top

Sheridan Australia Pty Ltd ABN 89 094 091 380

Latest Revision: May 2018
